mobiledokan.com 2018-07-04

# Privacy Policy | MobileDokan

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which MobileDokan.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.mobiledokan.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all services offered by MobileDokan.com.

## **Web browser cookies**

Our Site or programs used within our site (such as Google Adsense, Google Analytics etc.) may use “cookies” to collect user/visitor data to analyze ad performance, serving banner ads that are relevant to your interest, to analyze traffic, enhance user experience and to protect your data. A cookie is a small piece of text sent to your browser when you visit our website. This will record information about your visit which will help us serve more relevant and interesting content and ads to you. A user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent.

Additionally, if you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

## **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

## **Personal identification information**

We don’t have any contact form, Email newsletter subscription form or transaction form on our website. The only way to identify your personal information on our site is via the comment you make. This includes the name you provide, your Email address and the comment you make. See the “Comments” section below for more information.

## **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site via Google Analytics, Google Adsense and Google Tag Manager. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of device, country, operating system and the Internet service provider and similar technical information of the Users. The Users remains anonymous to us when they send non-personal information via those third-party services and MobileDokan.com do not have any way to identify the Users via non-personal identification information.

## **How we use collected information**

MobileDokan collects only non-personal information:

– To improve our Site and provide a more personalized user experience  
We use the non-personal identification information to understand our user’s needs and to fix technical errors on our site.

## **How we protect your information**

We use a username, secure password, website firewall and other advanced security measures to protect our website and any data you may provide to us.

## **Sharing your personal information**

MobileDokan.com do not sell, trade, rent or share any of your information for any purpose. Third-party programs like Google Analytics may analyze your non-personal information.

## **Comments**

When you make a comment on our site, your name, Email and content are saved on our site. We do not use this information for any purpose. Third-party service Akismet anti-spam also checks your comments for spam and may save them in their server. You may send an Email to mail(at)mobiledokan(dot)com and request to delete your comment, name and Email address. We will try to delete it from our database and site within 48 hours and notify you via Email once it is done.

## **What data breach procedures we have in place**

We don’t collect any sensitive data such as Address, credit card information, date of birth, ID card etc. from Users hence, we don’t have any procedure for a data breach.

## **Changes to this privacy policy**

MobileDokan has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
mail(at)mobiledokan(dot)com

**This document was last updated on May 24, 2018**

Dec 1, 2014
